英文字幕: Horriblesubs
中文字幕: 布尔
本字幕参照英文字幕制作
可能会由于
1. 日译英的瑕疵
2. 英译汉的瑕疵
而产生偏差
请根据自己情况使用
或者等待更精确的版本
Use it at your own risk
我想被连接啊
急救中心
So heavy, dish...
太重了 dish……
第一颗星
水獭
最爱
第一
没问题
最爱
水獭部落
This isn't fair.
怎么会这样
No!
不要啊
Once the background blends together,there's an invisible street corner
There we are, crying out with fading voices
Go forth with the tearing pain
As though you'd just crawledaway from the worst night ever
You're always alone
Your heart is shouting a sound of desire
If we can ever talk again,if we can ever connect
I'd be overwhelmed
You grow more and more distant
I chase after you
To tell you my brand new feelings for you
I run like mad
Present, past and future
I want to be connected with you
By our feelings, by the depths of our souls
和平街道上的帮派火并？
连环枪击案
我以后再也不往拉面里放胡椒了 dish 我再也不会打喷嚏了 dish 我再也不会踢我的爱人了dish
Breaking news, dish.
紧急新闻 dish
A serial shooting has occurred this afternoon in Asakusa.
今天下午浅草地区发生了连环枪击案
连环枪击案
和平街道上的帮派火并？
我以后再也不往拉面里放胡椒了 dish 我再也不会打喷嚏了 dish 我再也不会踢我的爱人了dish
Of the two victims, one has passed away, and the other is in critical condition.
两起案件的受害者 一个已经死亡了 另一个意识不清的状态中
The deceased's identity is currently unknown.
死者的身份暂时无法确认
The boy in critical condition is Jinnai Enta-kun, 14 years old.
处在重伤状态的受害者是14岁的男孩阵内燕太
重伤状态
Hey, it's Specs.
嘿 这不是那位老哥吗
How come you know him?
哥哥你怎么知道他的
He helped me out with some stuff.
他帮了我忙
Was he your buddy?
他是你的朋友吗
和平街道上的帮派火并？
Wanted fugitive Kuji Chikai is suspected of having been involved with the incident.
通缉中的逃犯久慈誓被怀疑和案件有关
Come on. Not everything is my fault, damn it. Right?
不可能所有的事儿都怪到我头上嘛
You can go back if you want, you know.
如果你想回就回吧
If you want out, it's now or never.
也就现在你还有得选了
You can't go back later.
过会你就回不去了
和平街道上的帮派火并？
我以后再也不往拉面里放胡椒了 dish 我再也不会打喷嚏了 dish 我再也不会踢我的爱人了dish
Runaway!
快逃啊
Asakusa Sara TV.
浅草皿电视台
He has someone who's closer to him than I am.
他有更亲近的人惦记着
But I'm the only one who can be by your side.
但只有我能站在哥哥身边
The bad ones are the ones to survive in this world.
这个世界只有坏人才能生存下去
Specs was a good person. That's all.
那家伙是个好人 就这样吧
Please, Yasaka.
拜托你了 矢逆
It was a pair of cops who shot Enta!
是两个警察枪击的燕太
Enta protected me...
燕太保护了我……
Calm down, son.
小伙子你冷静点
The shooter was Kuji Chikai.
杀手是久慈誓
We lifted Kuji's fingerprints off the candies Enta-kun had.
我们从燕太的糖果上找到了久慈的指纹
That's not right!
不是这样的
I saw it with my own eyes!
我亲眼所见
The cops...
那些警察……
It's okay now, Kazu-kun.
没事啦 一稀
No, Sensei!
老师 不是这样的
I...
我……
You must have been scared.
你肯定是特别害怕吧
Thanks for helping Enta.
谢谢你帮助了燕太
It's my fault this happened to Enta!
燕太的事是我的错
You're not at fault.
不是你的错
Whoever shot Enta is.
错在枪击了燕太的犯人
Jinnai-san, this way, please.
阵内 这边请
I'll be right there.
我马上就来
Why won't anyone believe me?
为什么没人愿意相信我
Someone, please, help me.
谁来救救我
Toi...
悠……
Bro!
大哥
I told you to lay low, idiot.
混蛋 我跟你说了要低调点
Sorry.
抱歉
You were late, so I got worried.
你迟到了 所以我很担心你
This is my kid brother, Toi.
这是我弟弟悠
And this is Masa.
这个是雅
I'm Masa.
我是雅
I've been given the honor of taking care of your brother.
很荣幸能照看大哥你的弟弟
Nice to meet you, Toi-san.
请多指教 悠
Who's taking care of who?
是谁照看谁 啊?
Ow, man.
有点疼啦
Seriously, though.
话说回来
A middle school kid making bank on weed?
中学生通过烟草来赚钱吗
I can totally believe he's your brother.
不愧是大哥你的亲弟弟啊
I want some of that!
我也好想有点这种天赋
As you can see, he's a moron,but he's my little bro from the gang.
如你所见 这是个笨蛋 但也是我从帮派那里得到的一个小弟
You're about the same age.
和你差不多大
You'll get along.
你会很快和他交上朋友的
暖暖的
Mabu... Are you...
真武……你真的……
Are you my Mabu?
你真的是我的 真武吗
This is it.
这个味道
He's the real Mabu.
他是真的真武
Finally!
终于做到了
I finally have you back.
我终于让你回来了
Otters...
水獭……
Soiya!
诳呀
I'm not going to mess this up, dish.
我不会搞砸这个的 dish
Scalpel.
手术刀
Scissors.
剪刀
Glue.
胶水
万能胶
Pepper.
胡椒
This is the last piece, dish.
这是最后一片了 dish
Let's forced defrosting, dish.
我们来强制解冻吧 dish
Prince!
王子
I'm glad you're safe, dish...
我很高兴你安全了 dish……
I thought I was dead, kero.
我以为我死了 呱呱
What the hell is this?!
但这是怎么回事
You're beautiful no matter how you look, dish.
不管王子你长成什么样 都很美丽 dish
Have a free candy.
送一块糖
Thank you.
谢谢你
Merci.
谢谢
Your brother has some real balls.
你弟弟真有两下子的
He's special.
他是特别的
He's not like your average brat.
不像你手下的那些平庸之辈
I mean, he took out the head of Yurikamome when he was ten.
我是指他十岁的时候就干掉了新桥帮的头目
I told you, I was the one who killed him.
我跟你说了 那是我杀的
My bad.
我的锅
You brought the Kamome boss's balls to our pops.
你把那种杀掉新桥帮老大的胆量带给了我们
And that's how you came to be.
这就是大哥你的为人之道啊
Lucky for you that your brother did that for you, huh?
你弟弟帮你做了这事儿 对你而言不也是挺幸运的吗
Shut the hell up.
给我闭嘴
Ow!
好疼
I only said what's true!
我说的不过是事实而已啊
They said Enta might not make it through the night.
他们说燕太可能熬不过今天晚上了
No...
怎么会这样……
Kazu-kun, would you stay by his side and speak to him for me?
一稀 你能陪在他身边帮我说几句话吗
I...
我……
I don't have the right to talk to him.
我没有权利和他说话
That's not true.
不是这样的
He's indebted to you, and you're dear to him.
对燕太来说 一稀你是他的恩人
The people in our family get assigned to work overseas a lot.
我们家的人老在国外工作
It was four years ago that Enta and I came back to Asakusa.
四年前我和燕太回到浅草
He had a hard time fitting in with his classmates, apparently.
那孩子很难融入班级集体
But you see...
但是……
回想
Hey.
嘿
Want to pass the ball to me?
想给我传球吗
Huh? Me?
呃 我吗
You always watch us play soccer here, don't you?
你总是看我们踢球呢
I'll end up making you an outcast, too.
我最后肯定也会把大家搞砸的
You should pretend you have no business with me.
你应该假装和我没有关系
I totally have business with you.
关系大了去了
I want to play soccer with you.
我想和你一起踢球
The two of us can totally become a golden duo.
我俩一定能成为黄金搭档的
I'm Jinnai Enta.
我是阵内燕太
I'm Yasaka Kazuki.
我是矢逆一稀
Nice to meet you.
请多指教
Kazuki...
一稀……
He was really happy about that.
这件事上他真的很高兴
Enta told me...
燕太跟我说……
"I'm never going to let Kazuki become lonely."
我决不会让一稀孤单一人
"I'm always going to be by his side, no matter what."
不管发生什么 我都会支持他
What the hell...
这算什么……
This isn't like you.
这不像你
You go on and on about shit that doesn't matter,
你总是说些无关紧要的话
yet you get yourself hurt without telling me what's important.
不跟我说重要的事情 总是独自一人受伤
Wake up.
快醒醒
Smile like you always do, Enta.
像以往一样微笑吧 燕太
Did you call me?
你在叫我吗
'Sup.
Kappa...
哟
河童……
En—
燕
Shh!
嘘
My sister and the others will notice!
我姐姐和其他人会发现的
Enta...
燕太……
How?
怎么会
I gobbled him up and turned him into a kappa, kero.
我把他吞了变成了河童 呱呱
Keppi?!
keppi
Where've you been?
你之前去哪儿了
It's a long story, kero.
说来话长 呱呱
What's that sound?
这是什么声音
Huh?
呃
It sounds like a time bomb.
听起来像是定时炸弹
It's a timer that indicates how much longer Enta has to live.
这是一个显示燕太还能活多久的定时器
Seriously?!
不会吧？
I can't see it!
没机会了
Calm down, Enta.
冷静 燕太
We still have time.
我们还有时间
I'll save you, Enta.
我会救你的 燕太
We'll get the dishes of Hope back.
我们会拿回希望之皿的
Kazuki...
一稀……
But I ended up this way because I deserved it.
但这样下去就会因为我需要它所以才使用掉了
Like, it's none of your business.
和一稀你没有关系
It's totally my business.
关系大了去了
We're the golden duo, aren't we?
我们可是黄金搭档啊
K-Kazuki!
一稀
Kazuki! Kazuki, Kazuki!
一稀 一稀 一稀
Now that that's settled, we shall fight the decisive battle tonight, kero!
既然已经决定 那么今晚我们将决一死战 呱呱
Use this ticket to get to the island, and then transfer to another boat.
用这张票去岛上 然后再坐另一艘船
I owe you one.
我欠你个人情
It's not a big deal.
这没什么
Please take care.
请小心使用
I'm glad I got to meet you, too, Toi-san.
我也很荣幸见到你啊 悠
Thanks.
谢谢
Bro...
大哥……
Let's go.
我们走吧
The ship's leaving soon.
这船很快就离开了
Nii-san!
哥哥
Why do you have a gun?
你为啥拿着枪
Why did you shoot him?
你为啥开枪打了他
Masa wouldn't have survived in this world.
雅这种人就不该在这个世界上生存下去
That's why I did him the favor.
这就是为什么我来帮他的忙
That's all.
仅此而已
No way...
怎么会……
Damn it, now I have to deal with this asshole.
该死 现在该我来对付这个混蛋了
Bro, I've been waiting for you.
大哥 我一直都在等你
Taka!
鹰
How did you know to find me here?
你怎么找到我的
It's easy to find information about someone with as many enemies as you.
你这样的人树敌无数 自然很容易收集到你的情报
Wow, that hurts.
听起来怪伤人的
After how much I took care of you...
在我如此照顾你之后……
You shot Masa with that gun, didn't you?
你刚刚枪击了雅对吧
Killing your own people just to protect yourself...
只是为了保护自己而杀掉自己的人……
That does sound like you.
听起来确实像是你做的事
I make a point of using up my bullets early.
我特意早早用光了子弹
Otherwise, traitorous shitheads like you start popping up everywhere.
不然到处都会有像你这样的混蛋
This is the last time we'll hear your big mouth.
这将是我们最后一次听你那大嘴巴讲话了
You'll get killed by us or the fuzz'll catch you.
要么你被我们杀掉 要么你会被条子抓了
Either way, all that awaits you is hell.
不管哪种方式你都会下地狱
Not my problem.
这与我无关
I'm going to kill you all!
我要把你们全杀了
Shit.
该死
D-Dude...
你……
Run!
快跑
The two of us are a couple.
两人是情侣
The ultimate couple!
最棒的情侣
吾妻桥
Hey, sorry I'm back so late.
嘿 不好意思我来晚了
I brought home some of your favorite pancakes, so...
不过我带来了你最喜欢的煎饼
紧急情况下需要帮助 譬如犯罪或者意外事件 请使用这个电话打110 请直接和警察说
浅草警察署 川嘘站
Otter...
水獭……
Mabu?
真武？
You look like you're in otter agony, Mabu.
看起来你处在水獭的痛苦之中啊 真武
Yes...
对……
Please don't go.
请别这么做
Please watch me.
请看着我
地下街的吉祥物 水獭
Otter...
水獭……
As you wish.
如你所愿
What are those two doing?
他俩在干啥啊
Get away from Mabu!
快离开真武
Reo.
玲央
What the hell do you think you're doing to Mabu?!
你在对真武做什么
That's... me?
那是……我？
Otter...
水獭……
I am an otter.
我是个水獭
But I'm also you.
但我也是你
What do you mean by that?
你是指什么？
We otters exist in this world as concepts.
我们水獭在这个世界上以概念的形式存在
I am a mirror of the desires inside of you.
我是你内在欲望的一面镜子
Stop!
停下来
You're the one who wants to own Mabu, Reo.
玲央你就是那个想要拥有真武的人
You wanted to lock lips with this hollow machine.
你想要亲吻这空心的机器
Stop...
停下来……
You're merely being made to dance by your desires—by us otters.
你不过是被你自己的欲望 被我们水獭驱使着做事而已
Now, Mabu, what matters the most to you?
真武 现在对你来说最重要的是什么
Him?
他？
Or me?
还是我？
How do I look to you?
我该怎么看待你？
Right now, I need you.
我现在就需要你
没有开始
没有相连
没有终结
I knew you were an imposter.
我知道你就是个骗子
I was an idiot for believing you, even for a moment.
我真是个笨蛋 那一刻我竟然信了你
I'm going to take back the real Mabu with my own strength.
我要通过我自己的力量带回真正的真武
Just one more...
只要再来一个……
I just need one more dish of Hope.
只要再来一个希望之皿
Kazu-chan?
小一？
Sorry, did I wake you up?
对不起 我把你吵醒了吗
Are you going somewhere, Kazu-chan?
你要出去吗 小一？
Yeah.
对
Kinda.
就一会
Are you leaving without telling me again?
你又要不跟我说就离开我吗
I'm not that clueless anymore.
我可没有以前那么笨呢
You're right.
说的也是
Sorry.
对不起
I'm about to go help Enta.
我要帮助燕太
Is it dangerous?
危险吗？
It could be.
可能吧
But I've made up my mind.
但是我决定好了
This time, it's my turn to help him.
这次由我来拯救他
Enta-niichan always helped me, too.
燕太哥哥也经常帮助我
He was with me every week during rehab, too.
每周的康复治疗他都来帮我
I guess a lot happened that I didn't know about, huh?
我觉得还有很多事情我不知道吧
Enta-niichan and I had the same wish.
燕太哥哥和我有着一样的愿望
Isn't that awesome?
这样不好吗？
小一
我也在支持你
——燕太
Is this me?
这是我吗？
You're going to run again, aren't you?
小一 你又要跑起来了
You used to like this player before, remember?
你以前喜欢这个球星 还记得吗
回想
That's right, I did!
没错
I love it when you're running.
我喜欢你跑步的样子
I'll be waiting.
我会等着你的
I'll be back.
我会回来的
You only live once.
人生只有一次
You don't get extra lives.
可没有第二条生命
When things aren't working out, just throw it all away.
万事不顺的话  就把它们全部扔掉吧
Nii-san!
哥哥
Yo, I was worried.
我真的担心你
Are you all right?
你还好吧
Yeah.
恩
Why do you have that gun?
你为什么有那把枪
I swapped it out before you threw it out four years ago.
四年前 你扔掉之前我把它调包了
Not bad.
不错嘛
That's my kid brother for you.
不愧是我的弟弟
Are you going to throw me, your kid brother, out, too?
你也要把你的亲弟弟扔掉了吗
I don't care if you're a bad person to the core.
我不管你是不是个坏人
You're my brother, no matter what.
不管怎么样你都是我哥哥
You're a little too good to be my brother.
作为我弟弟 你也太好了点
The bad ones are the ones who survive in this world.
这个世界只有坏人才能生存下去
想要相连可是却又
难以传达
Stand by me
Please
I don't know if I can become stronger
The rain washes away my tears
I want to be embraced by your warmth
The flickering lightbulb that's been neglected
One morning, it had quietly died
It's almost like you and me
Like the fleeting moment whenwe held our hands together
I sat with my arms around my knees
Thinking of the days long gone
Stand by me
Please
I don't know if I can become stronger
Even if you aren't here now
Please give me the courage to reach out
Stand by you
Please
I want to get rid of everything
The rain washes away my tears
I just want to be embraced by your warmth
I did it!
我成功啦
Damn it...
该死
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
You need to get to a hospital.
你得去医院啊
Forget it.
算了吧
It won't matter.
这没关系的
Nii-san!
哥哥
I had everything planned to work out.
我做好了万全的计划
Stop talking already.
别说了
You ruined everything...
你搞砸了所有的东西……
I'm sorry.
对不起
So please...
所以请你……
Keep yourself fed with this.
用这个来养活自己吧
Son of a bitch...
混蛋……
It's such a pain in the ass,trying to connect...
为了联系却如此疼痛……
Fuck!
该死
本故事纯属虚构。
所有登场人物及团体均与现实无关。